<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>blog on pott.dev</title>
    <link>https://www.pott.dev/tags/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in blog on pott.dev</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 16:24:21 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.pott.dev/tags/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing myself</title>
      <link>https://www.pott.dev/blog/2019-05/introducing-myself/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 16:24:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.pott.dev/blog/2019-05/introducing-myself/</guid>
      <description>Who am I? My name is Johannes Ptaszyk.
I located and born in Bottrop, Germany and I identify as european.
Also I identify as the following:
 Software developer Political being Nature lover Music lover  What do I do? Currently I am working as a Junior in the Android development team at G Data Software AG.
I recently joined the german party Bündnis 90/Die Grünen to bring some new ideas to the german politics.
What is this website about? Mostly about me and my experiences and thoughts.
I am currently planing multiple sections and over time I might add more and more.
The main section will be the blog, where I will mostly write about technical stuff (e.g. Android Development or Hugo). This section will be mostly english.
There will be another section in the future where I write about politics that will most likely be written in german.
And then I plan on a third one that will be mostly creatvitiy related stuff like music, art or creating different kinds of things. Here I will have some german and some english posts depending on the topics.
Thank you Thank you for reading this small introduction about myself. I am looking forward to seeing comments on my posts and maybe I can even provide some useful stuff to you!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>